(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T17:39:32.849720",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox appears!
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
I'm the white-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki!
スック込んでちゃ始まらない
Sitting around won't get us started,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukong-bu too!
hi friends!! (yeah!!)
古今東西コーン茶をちーだい
From far and wide, give me some corn tea!
aiじゃないし得意はmc
Not AI, my specialty is MC!
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
I prefer golden koi over red love!
うちうちうちだぜ大神ミオだぜ
It's me, it's me, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼 (みおーん！)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めます like a ママ
I step in and stop you like a mom!
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop cackling!
つまり実はponってコト!?
Meaning, I'm actually a bit clumsy!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of doing light kick steps!
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future with tarot readings!
ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four together, Gamers are strongest!
君も遊ぼうぜbダッシュ
Let's play together with a B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Leveling up aiming for clear!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices in the simulation!
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, both newbies and vets!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games really are so much fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
(g.a.m.e.r.s)
いっくよーもぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go, mogu-mogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎりおにぎりはひいっどーぜーぞー
Onigiri onigiri is... here we go!
きらきらふらふらしゃ～ない猫だもん
Twinkling and swaying~ can't help it, I'm a cat!
ふーんそっかぁ僕でよくない？
Hmm is that so, aren't I good enough?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
Relaxed, slowly bouncing rhythm!
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Okayuism that totally affirms everything!
全行程効率ok
All processes efficient, OK!
毎日僕といーーっしょ！
Everyday togeeeether with me!
おぁよ～ゆびゆびワンワン
Ohayo~ yubi-yubi woof-woof!
パンをコネコネ厄神ころね
Kneading bread, Yakugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐くけれど圧かける
Affectionate, but puts pressure on you!
捗るインテンション
Progressing intention!
割れるリアクション
Explosive reaction!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer your finger? Streaming show!
わがったなーほーね指図厨おけい
Understood, right? Bossing me around is okay!
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
With all four together, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
If a flag pops up, collect it immediately!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and take a sniper shot!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復してしまう
We'll even restore your heart!
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting!
“耐久”っていうか止められない
It's less an "endurance" stream, more like I can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I just love games!
「突然ですが、ボーナeschallengeの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう( ´・ω・｀)」
"Suddenly, it's bonus challenge time! Let's respond loudly and aim for a high score ( ´・ω・｀)"
say!! こーんこっ！ (こーんこっ！)
Say!! Kon-kot! (Kon-kot!)
say!! みおーんみおん！ (みおーんみおん！)
Say!! Mio-n mion! (Mio-n mion!)
say!! もぐっもぐっ！ (もぐっもぐっ！)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!! ゆびっゆびっ！ (ゆびっゆびっ！)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
say!! こーんこっ！ (こーんこっ！)
Say!! Kon-kot! (Kon-kot!)
say!! みおーんみおん！ (みおーんみおん！)
Say!! Mio-n mion! (Mio-n mion!)
say!! もぐっもぐっ！ (もぐっもぐっ！)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!! ゆびっゆびっ！ (ゆびっゆびっ！)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
(perfect!!)
ゲーマーズ「おう～!!!!」
Gamers: "Ohh~!!!!"
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four together, Gamers are strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, Continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Never give up until 100% clear!
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices in the simulation!
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, both newbies and vets!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games really are so much fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こうして世界に平和が訪れたのであった――
And thus, peace came to the world--
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox appears!
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
I'm the white-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki!
スック込んでちゃ始まらない
Sitting around won't get us started,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukong-bu too!
hi friends!! (yeah!!)
古今東西コーン茶をちーだい
From far and wide, give me some corn tea!
aiじゃないし得意はmc
Not AI, my specialty is MC!
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
I prefer golden koi over red love!
うちうちうちだぜ大神ミオだぜ
It's me, it's me, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼 (みおーん！)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めます like a ママ
I step in and stop you like a mom!
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop cackling!
つまり実はponってコト!?
Meaning, I'm actually a bit clumsy!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of doing light kick steps!
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future with tarot readings!
ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four together, Gamers are strongest!
君も遊ぼうぜbダッシュ
Let's play together with a B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Leveling up aiming for clear!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices in the simulation!
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, both newbies and vets!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games really are so much fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
(g.a.m.e.r.s)
見守ってくれるから
Since you are watching over me,
歩んでいけるさ
I can walk forward,
(Go our way!) ワンダーなフィューチャー！
(Go our way!) A wonderful future!
Hi friends yeah!
せーの、1, 2, 3!
Let's go, 1, 2, 3!
そう始まりはこんこんと
Yes, the beginning is "kon-kon"
扉叩けば見慣れた顔いつもの場所
Knock on the door to familiar faces at the usual place.
集まればわいわいと
When we gather, we're noisy,
はしゃげまわるの獣だもん許してね
We're beasts running wild, so forgive us.
ああ楽しくてこの時が永遠に続きますように
Ah, it's so fun, I hope this time lasts forever.
これからもよろしくね
Please treat me well from now on too.
超最強！
Super strongest!
そう思えばながーいながーい付き合いだなって
When I think about it, we've known each other for so long.
超最高！
Super highest!
そろそろまた一緒にコラボしたいなって
It's about time we collaborated together again.
超最強！
Super strongest!
ほんとにーうに今日もかわいすぎるなって
Seriously, you're too cute today too.
超超最高！
Super super highest!
みんなすこだよ！ Go to the future!
I love you all! Go to the future!
きっと私達はどの瞬間も (Have fun!)
Surely, at every moment, we (have fun!)
忘れられない最強friends
Are the unforgettable strongest friends.
(どこにいてもちゃんと) 聞こえるから問題ないよ
(No matter where we are) I can hear you, so it's fine.
好き勝手やっちゃおうぜ (わいわいわいわいーっ！)
Let's do whatever we want (Wai wai wai wai!)
未来はいつでも驚きの連続で (Surprise!)
The future is always a series of surprises (Surprise!)
分かち合おうぜっずーっとさ
Let's share it forever.
ジグザグな道でもいいからさ
Even if it's a zigzag path,
笑顔で進んでいこう
Let's advance with a smile.
見守っているから歩んでいこうぜ
Since I am watching over you, let's walk forward.
行けるさどこまでもとどめどないワンダーなフィューチャー！
We can go anywhere to an endless wonderful future!
こんばんウルフ！2番は我々が乗っ取った！
"Konban-wolf!" We hijacked the second verse!
(なにすんの！？)
(What are you doing!?)
もぐもぐしっぽの全肯定じゃあ手始めに何しましょうか
"Mogu-mogu" tail, full approval, what shall we start with?
(こわいよ！？)
(It's scary!?)
あなたの心のひとさし指一日耐久配信だ！
Your heart's index finger, one-day endurance stream!
(むりむり)
(No way, no way)
てかその自己紹介わたしのじゃい！！！
Wait, that's my self-introduction!!!
(うわーーーーっ！)
(Waaaaaah!!!)
はいここでリセット！
Yes, reset here!
始まりはこんこんと
The beginning is "kon-kon"
扉叩けば奇想天外な日々楽しむしかない
Knock on the door and enjoy bizarre days.
もうずーっと私達はどの瞬間も (Look at!)
We will always be, at every moment (Look at!)
目が離せない永久friends
Unmissable eternal friends.
(今日も明日もその先も) 遊び尽くせばいいよ
(Today, tomorrow, and beyond) Just play to the fullest.
好きなだけ叫べ (わいわいわいわいーっ！)
Shout as much as you like (Wai wai wai wai!)
未来はいつでもワクワクの連鎖反応 (Excite!)
The future is always a chain reaction of excitement (Excite!)
繋げましょうずーっとさ
Let's connect it forever.
チグハグな私達だから
Because we are mismatched,
ハードなアドベンチャー全クリアできそうじゃん
It seems we can clear a hard adventure.
こんなにこんなに面白いきっかけてくれてありがとう
Thank you for giving us such an interesting trigger.
ずーっと僕らの大黒柱でいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for always being our backbone.
いつもいつも笑顔を絶やさないでいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for always keeping a smile on your face.
みんなみんなみんなすこだよ！！！ Go to the future!
Everyone, I love you all! Go to the future!
もっと面白くなるこの世界を駆け抜けようずーっとさ
Let's run through this exciting world forever.
予測不可能なカルテットどうそこれからもよろしくね ああ
Unpredictable quartet, please continue to treat us well.
きっと私達はどの瞬間も忘れられない最強friends
Surely, at every moment, we are unforgettable friends.
(どこにいてもちゃんと) 聞こえるから問題ないよ
(No matter where we are) I can hear you, so it's fine.
好き勝手やっちゃおうぜ (わいわいわいわいーっ！)
Let's do whatever we want (Wai wai wai wai!)
未来はいつでも驚きの連続で (Surprise!)
The future is always a series of surprises (Surprise!)
分かち合おうぜっずーっとさ
Let's share it forever.
ジグザグな道でもいいからさ
Even if it's a zigzag path,
笑顔で進んでいこう
Let's advance with a smile.
見守っているから歩んでいこうぜ
Since I am watching over you, let's walk forward.
行けるさどこまでもとどめどないワンダーなフィューチャー！
We can go anywhere to an endless wonderful future!
(もういいっちょ)
(One more time)
最高だぜワンダーなフィューチャー！ Yeah!
You're the best, wonderful future! Yeah!
ホロライブゲーマーズ!
Hololive Gamers!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こーん!とキツネが登場
"Kon!" A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
White-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki here.
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
Can't get started if you're holding back,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukong-bu too!
hi friends!! (yeah!!)
古今東西コーン茶をぢょーだい
Corn tea from all over, please!
aiじゃないし得意はmc
Not AI, and my specialty is MC.
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
Preferring a golden carp over red love,
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ
It's us, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼(みおーん!)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めますlike aママ
Stopping you with tsukkomis like a mom.
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop giggling,
つまり実はponってコト!?
Meaning I'm actually a bit clumsy!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of tiptoeing steps,
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future through tarot readings,
ホラーゲームはやしたくない!
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all 4 together, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよbダッシュ
Come play with us, B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Leveling up to aim for clear,
今日は何プレしようか
What should we play today?
君のハートも攻略してしまう
Conquering your heart as well,
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices and simulating,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike,
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
(g.a.m.e.r.s)
いっくよーもぐもぐ～猫又おかゆ
Here we go, mogumog～ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎりおにぎりはいいどうぞー
Onigiri onigiri, here you go～
きらきらふらふらしちゃうな猫だもん
Glittering and swaying, 'cause I'm a cat!
ふーんそっかぁ僕でよくない?
Hmm, is that so? Isn't I good enough?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
Relaxed, leisurely bouncing rhythm,
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Okayuism that affirms everything,
全行程効率ok
All processes efficient, OK!
毎日僕といーーっしょ!
Together with me everyday!
おぁよーゆびゆびワンワン
Ohayou, yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種:キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
懐くけど圧かける
Affectionate yet putting pressure,
震えるイントネーション
Trembling intonation,
割れるリアクション
Shattering reaction!
まずは指を捧げてくれる?配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがっかなーほーね指示厨おけ
Understood～? Bone, backseaters OK!
好物のレトロゲーお届き
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
With all 4 together, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
Collecting flags as soon as they're set!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot your target,
今日は何プレしようか
What should we play today?
君のハートを回復してしまう
Restoring your heart as well,
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting,
“耐久”というか止められない
It's less "endurance" than just unstoppable,
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
'Cause we just love games!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。
Sudden news! It's bonus challenge time.
大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう( ´・ω・｀)｣
Let's shout out loud responses and aim for a high score!
say!!こーんこーんっ!(こーんこーんっ!)
Say!! Kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
say!!みおーんみおーん!(みおーんみおーん!)
Say!! Mio-n mio-n! (Mio-n mio-n!)
say!!もぐっもぐっ!(もぐっもぐっ!)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!!ゆびっゆびっ!(ゆびっゆびっ!)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
say!!こーんこーんっ!(こーんこーんっ!)
Say!! Kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
say!!みおーんみおーん!(みおーんみおーん!)
Say!! Mio-n mio-n! (Mio-n mio-n!)
say!!もぐっもぐっ!(もぐっもぐっ!)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!!ゆびっゆびっ!(ゆびっゆびっ!)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
(perfect!!)
ゲーマーズ「おおう!!!!」
Gamers: "Woah!!!!"
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all 4 together, Gamers are the strongest!
上手くいかなくてもコンテニュー
Continuing even if things don't go well,
全クリアするまで諦めない
Never giving up until 100% clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略してしまう
Conquering your heart as well,
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices and simulating,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike,
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こうして世界に平和が訪れたのであった――
And thus, peace visited the world――
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こーん!とキツネが登場
"Kon!" A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
White-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki here.
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
Can't get started if you're holding back,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukong-bu too!
hi friends!! (yeah!!)
古今東西コーン茶をぢょーだい
Corn tea from all over, please!
aiじゃないし得意はmc
Not AI, and my specialty is MC.
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
Preferring a golden carp over red love,
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ
It's us, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼(みおーん!)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めますlike aママ
Stopping you with tsukkomis like a mom.
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop giggling,
つまり実はponってコト!?
Meaning I'm actually a bit clumsy!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of tiptoeing steps,
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future through tarot readings,
ホラーゲームはやしたくない!
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all 4 together, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよbダッシュ
Come play with us, B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Leveling up to aim for clear,
今日は何プレしようか
What should we play today?
君のハートも攻略してしまう
Conquering your heart as well,
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices and simulating,
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike,
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
(g.a.m.e.r.s)
いっくよーもぐもぐ～猫又おかゆ
Here we go, mogumog～ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎりおにぎりはいいどうぞー
Onigiri onigiri, here you go～
きらきらふらふらしちゃうな猫だもん
Glittering and swaying, 'cause I'm a cat!
ふーんそっかぁ僕でよくない?
Hmm, is that so? Isn't I good enough?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
Relaxed, leisurely bouncing rhythm,
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Okayuism that affirms everything,
全行程効率ok
All processes efficient, OK!
毎日僕といーーっしょ!
Together with me everyday!
おぁよーゆびゆびワンワン
Ohayou, yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種:キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel,
懐くけど圧かける
Affectionate yet putting pressure,
震えるイントネーション
Trembling intonation,
割れるリアクション
Shattering reaction!
まずは指を捧げてくれる?配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがっかなーほーね指示厨おけ
Understood～? Bone, backseaters OK!
好物のレトロゲーお届き
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
With all 4 together, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
Collecting flags as soon as they're set!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot your target,
今日は何プレしようか
What should we play today?
君のハートを回復してしまう
Restoring your heart as well,
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting,
“耐久”というか止められない
It's less "endurance" than just unstoppable,
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
'Cause we just love games!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。
Sudden news! It's bonus challenge time.
大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう( ´・ω・｀)｣
Let's shout out loud responses and aim for a high score!
say!!こーんこーんっ!(こーんこーんっ!)
Say!! Kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
say!!みおーんみおーん!(みおーんみおーん!)
Say!! Mio-n mio-n! (Mio-n mio-n!)
say!!もぐっもぐっ!(もぐっもぐっ!)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!!ゆびっゆびっ!(ゆびっゆびっ!)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
say!!こーんこーんっ!(こーんこーんっ!)
Say!! Kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
say!!みおーんみおーん!(みおーんみおーん!)
Say!! Mio-n mio-n! (Mio-n mio-n!)
say!!もぐっもぐっ!(もぐっもぐっ!)
Say!! Mogu-mogu! (Mogu-mogu!)
say!!ゆびっゆびっ!(ゆびっゆびっ!)
Say!! Yubi-yubi! (Yubi-yubi!)
(perfect!!)
ゲーマーズ「おおう!!!!」
Gamers: "Woah!!!!"
ホロライブゲーマーズ!
Hololive Gamers!
(g.a.m.e.r.s) we are gamers!!!!
こーん!とキツネが登場
"Kon!" A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
White-haired kemonomimi, Shirakami Fubuki here.
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
Can't get started if you're holding back,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukong-bu too!
hi friends!! (yeah!!)
古今東西コーン茶をぢょーだい
Corn tea from all over, please!
aiじゃないし得意はmc
Not AI, and my specialty is MC.
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
Preferring a golden carp over red love,
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ
It's us, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼(みおーん!)
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めますlike aママ
Stopping you with tsukkomis like a mom.
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop giggling,
Are you free tonight?
Called from you, now
お気に入りムスクと甘々な秘密纏う
I'm clad in my favourite musk and my sweet secret
I've been waiting... This weekend night!!
今夜モノになる あたしのなにもかも
I'll make this night my own with everything I have!
溢れ出してる libido は好い好きその衝動
My libido is overflowing... ah, how I love that urge
そんななら見て見てよ
Well then, just watch
伝家の宝刀
as my last resort
いこう王道
becomes the fast track to success
「はあ ちょっと酔っちゃったかも」
Ah... I might be a little drunk
すべて見抜いて
I see through it all.
余裕なんて見せないで
Don't show me some facade of composure
すべて見通して
I see through the true nature of it all
好きにさせて
Let me do as I please!
ねえ早く連れていって
Come on, hurry, take me along.
まつげすら触れちゃいそうな距離で
Close enough that our eyelashes could almost touch
思考すら奪い取って 探り当てて
I'll steal even your thoughts and figure you out!
其処場凌ぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
It seems like I've said more than I needed to
吐息漏れるこの唇をキスで塞いで
Please shut these sighing lips with a kiss
I just Gimme×Gimme
余計なこと考えてないで
Don't think about unnecessary things
今は踊りましょう シャバダバダ ドゥビドゥビドゥ
Right now, let's just dance shabadabada du bidu bidu
映画のエンディングみたいに背中の跡過去重ね数え
Like the end credits of a movie, the marks on my back piled up
酔いも醒めないフリで
Drunk and pretending not to sober up
宵々からの夜が明けてく
night comes upon us from a good evening
足りないくらいが丁度いい…
It's perfect when it's just not enough...
なんて意地悪ばかり言わないで！
Don't say such mean things!
まだまだ足りないこれは純愛
It's still not enough. This is pure love
好きにさせて
Let me do as I please!
ねえ早く連れていって
Come on, hurry, take me along.
微熱で溶けちゃいそうな距離で
Close enough that you could almost melt from the heat
思考すら奪い取って 貫いてって
I'll steal even your thoughts and pierce right through you!
其処場凌ぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
It seems like I've said more than I needed to
吐息漏れるその唇で
I'll plug my ears with your sighing lips
耳を塞いで
Stop this moment
この時も
and our breath
呼吸も止めて
Fill the hole in my burning heart
火照る心の隙間埋めて
Give me a reason to be here
ここにいる意味を成して
I don't care about the future
未来なんていらない
Just look at me right now!
今のあたしを見て！
I just wanna×wanna
I just Wanna×Wanna
Let me do as I please!
好きにさせて
Come on, hurry, take me along.
ねえ早く連れていって
Close enough that our eyelashes could almost touch
まつげすら触れちゃいそうな距離で
I'll steal even your thoughts and figure you out!
思考すら奪い取って 探り当てて
It seems like I've said more than I needed to
其処場凌ぎ以上の余計なこと言っちゃいそうだな
Please shut these sighing lips with a kiss
吐息漏れるこの唇をキスで塞いで
Coloured vibrantly
鮮やかに彩って
Forget what I just said
As if to light up this world
この世界を照らすような
Actually, don't forget
Until I've had my fill of body heat
満たす体温最後まで
Please, don't forget... lifetime
Please don't forget... lifetime
Please shut these sighing lips with a kiss
吐息漏れるこの唇をキスで塞いで
Don't want to go home
But I have to
Because he comes home
Maybe next time
(G.A.M.E.R.S) We are GAMERS!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場
"Kon!" A fox appears!
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキです
White-haired kemonomimi, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
Staying hidden won't get us started,
君もすこん部に 入部しなさい
so you should join the Sukon-bu too!
Hi friends!
(Yeah!)
古今東西 ほうじ茶をちょーだい
From east to west, give me hojicha!
AIじゃないし得意はMC
I'm not AI, my specialty is MC.
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
Rather than red romance, golden carp is my favorite!
うちうちうちだよ
It's us, us, us!
大神ミオだよ
It's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ 狼
Black-haired kemonomimi wolf—
ツッコミで止めます like a ママ
Stopping the tsukkomi like a mom!
笑い出すと止まらないゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop giggling,
つまり実はponってコト！？
meaning I'm actually a bit clumsy!?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of quick little steps,
タロット占いで見る未来
seeing the future through tarot cards.
ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよBダッシュ
Come play with us, B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Level up aiming for a clear,
今日は何プレイしよう
what shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択肢を選んでシミュレーション
Choose options and simulate.
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games are really so much fun!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
We are GAMERS!!!!
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go! Mogu mogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりはっぴーだぞー
Onigiri, onigiri is so happy~
きらきらふらふら しゃーない猫だもんね
Sparkling, fluttering, can't be helped, I'm a cat!
ふーん そうかぁ ぼくでよくない？
Hmm, is that so? Isn't I fine for you?
まったりゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Relaxed and slow, a bouncing rhythm.
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Okayu'sism of total affirmation!
全行程効率OK 毎日僕といーっしょ！
All-process efficiency OK, be with me every day!
(ころね)
Korone!
おぁょ～ ゆびゆびワンワン
Oahyo~ Yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種:キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐くけれど圧かける
Affectionate, but applying pressure!
揺るぎないイントネーション
Unshakable intonation,
割れるリアクション
explosive reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがったなーほーね 指示厨おけ
Got it, ho-ne! Backseaters are okay!
好物のレトロゲーお届き
Delivering favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
Collect flags as soon as they're raised!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and take the shot!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復してしまう
We'll even restore your heart!
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting!
"耐久"っていうか止められない
"Endurance"? More like we can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう！
Now then, it's bonus challenge time! Let's shout loudly for high scores!
(Are you ready?)
say! こーん こーんっ!
Say! Kon kon!
(こーん こーんっ!)
(Kon kon!)
say! みおーん みおーん!
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーん みおーん!)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say! もごっ もごっ!
Say! Mogu mogu!
(もごっ もごっ!)
(Mogu mogu!)
say! ゆびっ ゆびっ!
Say! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびっ ゆびっ!)
(Yubi yubi!)
say! こーん こーんっ!
Say! Kon kon!
(こーん こーんっ!)
(Kon kon!)
say! みおーん みおーん!
Say! Mio-n mio-n!
(みおーん みおーん!)
(Mio-n mio-n!)
say! もごっ もごっ!
Say! Mogu mogu!
(もごっ もごっ!)
(Mogu mogu!)
say! ゆびっ ゆびっ!
Say! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびっ ゆびっ!)
(Yubi yubi!)
(Perfect!)
ゲーマーズ「おおう!!!!」
Gamers: "Ohhh!!!!"
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Don't give up until a complete clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択肢を選んでシミュレーション
Choose options and simulate.
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games are really so much fun!
(G.A.M.E.R.S) We are GAMERS!!!!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
おぁょ～ ゆびゆびワンワン
Oahyo~ Yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種:キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐くけれど圧かける
Affectionate, but applying pressure!
揺るぎないイントネーション
Unshakable intonation,
割れるリアクション
explosive reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Streaming show!
わがったなーほーね 指示厨おけ
Got it, ho-ne! Backseaters are okay!
好物のレトロゲーお届き
Delivering favorite retro games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
Collect flags as soon as they're raised!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and take the shot!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復してしまう
We'll even restore your heart!
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting!
"耐久"っていうか止められない
"Endurance"? More like we can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
突発で出ます、お散歩チャレンジの時間よ！
Now then, it's time for a walk challenge!
Are you ready?
ゴー！ゴー！
Go! Go!
にゃんにゃん！にゃんにゃん！
Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!
でんもくもく！でんもくもく！
Den moku moku! Den moku moku!
ゆびゆび！ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!
ゴー！ゴー！
Go! Go!
にゃんにゃん！にゃんにゃん！
Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!
でんもくもく！でんもくもく！
Den moku moku! Den moku moku!
ゆびゆび！ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!
うりゅりゅー！
Uryuryu!
突発で出ます！ド直球チャレンジの時間よ！
Now then, it's a direct challenge time!
大きな声でレスポンスをして孤独厨を狙えちゃいましょう！
Let's shout loudly and aim for high scores!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ゴー！ゴー！
Go! Go!
(ゴー！ゴー！)
(Go! Go!)
にゃーにゃー！ にゃーにゃー！
Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!
(にゃーにゃー！ にゃーにゃー！)
(Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!)
でんもくもく！ でんもくもく！
Den moku moku! Den moku moku!
(でんもくもく！ でんもくもく！)
(Den moku moku! Den moku moku!)
ゆびゆび！ ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびゆび！ ゆびゆび！)
(Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!)
ゴー！ゴー！
Go! Go!
(ゴー！ゴー！)
(Go! Go!)
にゃーにゃー！ にゃーにゃー！
Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!
(にゃーにゃー！ にゃーにゃー！)
(Nyan nyan! Nyan nyan!)
でんもくもく！ でんもくもく！
Den moku moku! Den moku moku!
(でんもくもく！ でんもくもく！)
(Den moku moku! Den moku moku!)
ゆびゆび！ ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびゆび！ ゆびゆび！)
(Yubi yubi! Yubi yubi!)
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
With all four, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリアするまで諦めない
Don't give up until a complete clear,
エンディングを見に行こう
let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略してしまう
We'll even conquer your heart too!
選択肢を選んでシミュレーション
Choose options and simulate.
初見も古参も対よろ
Nice to meet you, newbies and veterans alike!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games are really so much fun!
(G.A.M.E.R.S) We are GAMERS!!!!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
こうして世界に平和が訪れたのであった――
And thus, peace came to the world—
うおおおー！
Woohoo!
ホロライブゲーマーズです！
We are Hololive GAMERS!
(G.A.M.E.R.S) we are gamers!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Corn! A fox appears
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキです
White-haired kemomimi, Shirakami Fubuki
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
It doesn't start if you stay hidden
君もすこん部に加入しなさい
You should join the Sukonbu club too
hi friends!!
(yeah!!)
古今東西 コーン茶をちょーだい
Give me corn tea from all over the world
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
Not an AI, my specialty is MC
赤い恋より 金の鯉が推し
I prefer gold carp over red love
うちうちうちだよ 大神ミオだよ
It's me, me, me, Ookami Mio
黒髪ケモミミ 狼（みおーん！）
Black-haired kemomimi wolf (Mio-n!)
ツッコんで止めます like a ママ
I'll tsukkomi and stop it like a mama
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
When I start laughing, I can't stop, gera gera
つまり実はポンってコト!?
In other words, it's actually pon!?
小足ステップしてしまう音
Steps on small feet
タロット占いで見る未来
Future seen by tarot fortune telling
ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
If the 4 of us are together, GAMERS is the strongest
君も遊ぼうよ bダッシュ
Let's play together, B dash
クリア目指して レベル上げ
Aiming for clear, level up
本日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today
君のハートも攻略してしまう
I'll capture your heart too
選択をして シミュレーション
Choose and simulate
初見も古参も 対よろ
First timers and old timers, please treat me well
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun, aren't they
(G.A.M.E.R.S) we are gamers!!!!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Let's go, Mogu-Mogu~ Nekomata Okayu
おにぎり おにぎりはいいくどうぞー
Rice ball, rice ball, here you go~
きらきら ふらふら しゃ～ない猫だもん
Sparkling, wandering, can't help it, I'm a cat
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, I see, isn't it fine if it's me?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Lazy, slow, bouncing rhythm
全肯定する おかゆイズム
Okayu-ism that affirms everything
全行程効率 ok
All processes are efficient, ok
毎日 僕とい～～っしょ！
Every day together with me!!
おぁょ～ ゆびゆび ワンワン
O-a-yo~ Yubi-Yubi, Wan-Wan
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Dog breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel
懐くけど 圧かける
I get attached, but I put pressure
訛るイントネーション
Accented intonation
割れるリアクション
Cracking reaction
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ 配信ショー
First, will you offer your finger? Streaming show
わがったなー ほーね 指示厨おけい
I got it, bone, instruction chef is ok
好物のレトロゲー お届け
Delivering my favorite retro games
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最高
If the 4 of us are together, GAMERS is the best
フラグが立てば すぐ回収
If a flag is set, I'll collect it immediately
エイム鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot
本日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today
君のハートを回復してしまう
I'll recover your heart
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
It's exciting, this dungeon
“耐久”っていうか 止められない
'Endurance' or rather, can't stop
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I love games
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう( ´･ω･` )」
(Bonus challenge time! Let's respond loudly!)
say!! こーんこーんっ！
Say!! Corn Corn!!
(こーんこーんっ！)
(Corn Corn!!)
say!! みおーんみおーんっ！
Say!! Mio-n Mio-n!!
(みおーんみおーんっ！)
(Mio-n Mio-n!!)
say!! もごっもごっっ！
Say!! Mogu Mogu!!
(もごっもごっっ！)
(Mogu Mogu!!)
say!! ゆびっゆびっっ！
Say!! Yubi Yubi!!
(ゆびっゆびっっ！)
(Yubi Yubi!!)
(perfect!!)
ゲーマーズ「お～!!!!」
GAMERS: "Oh~!!!!"
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
If the 4 of us are together, GAMERS is the strongest
上手く行かなくても コンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue
全クリアするまで 諦めない
I won't give up until I clear everything
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending
君のハートも攻略してしまう
I'll capture your heart too
選択をして シミュレーション
Choose and simulate
初見も古参も 対よろ
First timers and old timers, please treat me well
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, games are fun, aren't they
(G.A.M.E.R.S) we are gamers!!!!
こうして世界に平和が訪れたのであった―――
Thus, peace visited the world---
えーなんと、day1、day2あわせると
Um, combining day 1 and day 2,
なんと3万5...約3万5000人以上が
over 35... about 35,000 people
7000人ぐらい来てるですよ
about 7,000 people are here!
いーーー！すごい！
Waaaah! Amazing!
どうなってるの！？すごいねー！
How is this possible?! Amazing!
すごい上の方もみんな
Even those way up top, everyone
いますよあそこ！いーやーまー！
are over there! Yay!
見えてる？そこ
Can you see us? Over there
見えてるー！大丈夫です！
We can see you! Everything's fine!
三階！おー！
Third floor! Oh!
左右も見えてますかー！
Can the sides see us too?!
見えてるかー！すごいですよもう！
Can you see?! This is amazing!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
ところでねはですね、あのー
By the way, um,
みおがこれなかった
Mio couldn't make it
で、今回は大きな場所でやらせていただくことになりまして
so this time we got to do it in such a huge place...
1回目やらせていただけて本当はねありがと、ほんとにみなさんに感謝です、おかげさまでライブも開催することができました
We really wanted to do it... thanks to everyone.
よかったよかった！おかげだ！なんのおかげだ！ありがとうございます！
Good for you! Thanks to everyone!
さて改めてましてこのイベントではゲームが大好きな我々を中心に...
Now again, this event centers around us who love games...
様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントとなってまーす！
taking on various game titles and delivering live performances...
しかも今回ですね、皆様お分かりかと思いますがday1に引き続き4人の
And this time, as you all know, continuing from Day 1...
おそろいTシャツ！いぇーい！かわいいー！
matching T-shirts! Yay! So cute!
ひっぴーさーびすね！チポサービス中！ちぽさーびすちゅう！
Hippie service! Chippo service in progress!
さらにさらに会場ではですね、一部撮影OKなパートがありますので、そちらもお楽しみに！
Furthermore, at the venue, there's a part where photography is allowed...
ぜひ最後まで皆さん盛り上がっていきますかー！うー！ありがとうございます！
Are you all going to keep the hype up till the end?!
ということでね、我々ゲーマーズからも1人ずつ意気込みを言っていきたいと思いますよ！ではは！
Now, we Gamers will each share our enthusiasm...
最終日、まずはミオから！はーい！
Final day, starting with Mio! Yes!
えーっとですね、昨日あの意気込みで、あの明日も
Um, yesterday with that enthusiasm...
体調を崩さないように頑張るっていう風にね、
I promised to do my best not to fall out of shape,
気負わせていただいたんですけど、
and really put my heart into it, but...
もう今日はのこの会場にね、あのもういてここステージに立ってるということは
Now that we're here at this venue today and standing on this stage,
どんなに体調を崩そうとも帰れないということなんだよね
no matter how unwell I feel, there's no turning back!
やめて！体調崩して！
Stop it! Don't feel unwell!
やめて！やめて！やめないで！
Stop! Don't stop!
さ、最後まで笑顔で走り切る、頑張りたいと思います。
I want to keep smiling all the way to the finish line and do my best.
みんな一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
Let's all get excited together!
はい。昨日はね、逆逆日立3割の目標に大谷翔平ね、頑張ったんですけど
Yesterday, my goal was a .300 average like Shohei Ohtani, and I worked hard, but...
ちょっと逆に頑張りすぎて、微妙にできかけになったので
I guess I worked a bit too hard in reverse, and ended up feeling slightly...
今日は、ほどほどに、逆にほどほどに楽しんでいきたいと思います。
So today, I want to enjoy myself in moderation, well, just moderately.
ほどほどは
Moderately...
2.5、いや昨日なんだ、どうだったんだ。
2.5? Wait, what happened yesterday?
死ぬ気ですごい広いホームランの内容を受けたんですけど、なんか点数引くとかさ、
I hit a huge home run as if my life depended on it, but somehow my points got deducted...
点数引かれたりとかさ、日本語に？
Points were deducted, and... Wait, in Japanese?
どんなんでしたっけ？
How was it again?
で、またどうなんだ、どうなんでしたっけ。足首3割だろっていうことやらされたんですけど、
And what was it again? They made me do something like 'ankle 300', but what was that?
どうなんでしたっけ。やだ！やんない！
No way! I won't do it!
なんか、なんかいでもスーパーリーナで歌わされたりさ、進めとかさ、かわして、かわして！って、恐ろしかったよな。心拍数は高かったです。
Being forced to sing 'Super Rina' repeatedly, or told 'advance' and 'dodge, dodge!'—it was terrifying. My heart rate was high.
そしてね、次は大谷さんの話をしていた。
And next, we were talking about Ohtani.
昨日ね、これで昨日ね、ちょっと翔平のためにとか言って、自分のこの日数がね、
Yesterday, you know, saying it was for Shohei, my number of days...
そのために、今日もね、この日数のために頑張ります！あつばわーい！
For that reason, I'll do my best for this number of days today too! Yay!
え、白上もですね、今日もですね、たくさん歌い上げることが多いと思うんですけども、その間ね、あの、
Um, as for Fubuki, I think I'll have a lot of songs to sing today too, but in the meantime...
この3人がきっといっぱい面白おかしいことやってくれるんじゃないかと思っておりますので、白上のお話にも耳を傾けつつ、
I'm sure these three will do lots of funny things, so while listening to Fubuki's talk,
おめめはですね、あの上の大きいモニターと、そしてあの可愛い3人を見ていただいて、最後みんなでね笑って帰れるといいなと思ってますので、よろしくお願いします！
please keep your eyes on the big monitor above and the three cute girls, and hopefully we can all go home smiling at the end!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
そして、昨日と今日行われる超超超ゲーマーズ2は、ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！コメントの民みんな見てる？
And, Chochoucho Gamers 2 held yesterday and today is live-streamed on ABEMA PPV! Is everyone in the comments watching?
見えてるよ！見えてる見えてる！
We see it! We can see it!
翔平の2割だろってコメントもね。ありがとうございます！
There are comments like 'It's Ohtani's 200'. Thank you very much!
配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！イベントが終わっても8月4日月曜日の23時59分までなんと見返すことができます！
Streaming tickets are now on sale! Even after the event ends, you can rewatch it until 11:59 PM on Monday, August 4th!
さらに、特典としてデイ1とデイ2で異なる出演の限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
Furthermore, as a bonus, limited original voice dramas featuring different appearances for Day 1 and Day 2 will be included!
デイ1は秘密の事前プロデュースボイス、デイ2は内緒の超内緒のおまけおつかれさまボイス！内緒ってどの程度内緒なんですか？
Day 1 is 'Secret Pre-Produced Voice', Day 2 is 'Super Secret Bonus Good Work Voice'! Just how secret is 'secret'?
絶対内緒だよ！内緒だよ！
It's an absolute secret! A secret!
さらに、我々からのエチケットメッセージのライブ画像、ライブ画像ってなんだ？エチケットメッセージのライブ画像もついてきますので
In addition, live images of etiquette messages from us—wait, what's a 'live image of an etiquette message'?—will also be included,
ぜひチェックしてみてくださいね。お願いします！
so please be sure to check them out. Thank you!
さらに昨年行われました超超超ゲーマーズのダイジェストがABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！昨年のね楽しかった、ちょっと見よわ、
Furthermore, the digest of 'Chochoucho Gamers' held last year is now available on ABEMA Premium! Last year was so fun, let's watch a bit—
みなさんでもね、頑張らせていただきますので、その様子いっぱい見てください！
we'll do our best for everyone too, so please watch lots of that!
ほい、さらにさらにイベント後にグッズの受注販売が開催中です！こちらの期間は7月21日の23時59分まで！Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中で、10月中旬頃からお届けです！
And what's more, goods mail-order sales are currently open after the event! This period runs until July 21st at 11:59 PM! Accepting orders at the Cyber Goods Store, delivery starting around mid-October!
こちらも予約したお方いますか？どうかな？結構買っちゃってるんじゃないの？買ってるけどみんなほら良くしてるって全然。
Did anyone reserve these too? How is it? Aren't you buying quite a lot? Well, everyone's doing great...
お味ごちそうさまありがとうございました！そして当日販売のグッズはすべて売り切れとのことですみなさんありがとうございました！
Thank you for the meal/review! And all goods for same-day sales are sold out, thank you everyone!
びっくりじゃあ、みなさん本当にランダムでおしげとできたかい？できたかできたできたよかった！ありがとうございました！
Surprising! Everyone, were you really able to get Oshi items at random? Did you manage it? Yay, wonderful! Thank you very much!
まだゲットできなかったっていう方がいらっしゃいましたらね、ECサイトの事後通販で受注販売しておりますのでゲットしてください。
If there's anyone who couldn't get it yet, it's available via post-event online mail-order, so please go get it!
そしてさらにさらにさらに！もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが、NTTドコモさんの「home 5G」とコラボキャンペーン実施中です！
And even more, even more, even more! As some of you may already know, a collaboration campaign with NTT docomo's "home 5G" is underway!
え、デカタオルや入り口でもらえるうちわは皆さんゲットしましたか？ちゃんとやりましたよって人！
Have you all gotten the giant towel and the fan you get at the entrance? Who actually did it?
お、いらっしゃいます、ありがとうございます！
Oh, there are some! Thank you very much!
受注終了日まで満点にして最後までお楽しみください！ありがとうございます！
Please enjoy it to the fullest until the end of the order period! Thank you!
あ、すいません！こちらですね、事後限定グッズとしましてアクリルパネルが追加されてるんです、皆さん知ってました？
Ah, excuse me! An acrylic panel has been added as a post-event limited item here. Did you all know about that?
そう、実はアクリルパネル！こちらね、あの事後限定グッズなので、今「はっ、そういえば！」って思った方は是非とも、あの、あの是非ゲットしてください！あの、あの、やめてー！
That's right, actually an acrylic panel! Since this is a post-event limited item, if you just thought, "Oh, come to think of it!", please, um, please go get it! Um, um, stop itー!
ごめんなさい！え、まだまだ続きますからね！
Sorry! Hey, there's still more to come!
え、我々ゲマズを応援したいという声が多かったので、今回のイベントで「CheerSPOT」さんとのコラボが決定！イェーイ！
Since there were so many voices wanting to support us Gamers, a collaboration with "CheerSPOT" has been decided for this event! Yay!
誰でも簡単に身近な「CheerSPOT」の場所に我々、我々の応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily put up our cheering ads at nearby "CheerSPOT" locations!
是非ともね、これ、あの白上も割と日々利用させていただいておりますので、よろしいですね。いや、ちゃ、違います。
We definitely use this quite often day-to-day too, so it's good... No, wait, that's wrong.
この画面上でもですね、設置してあるのを見たと思うんですけども、あんな感じでですね、すごく綺麗に広告出せますので、よければよろしくお願いいたします！
I think you saw it displayed on this screen too, but like that, you can put up ads really cleanly, so please check it out if you'd like!
え、さらにサテライトもスーパーアリーナ会場内で当日投影を初披露させていただきました！
Furthermore, satellite projection was premiered inside the Super Arena venue today!
3月のEXPO会場で発表された「フブミオ」当日投影に続きまして「おかころ」のフィギュアも発表されました、見てくれましたか？
Following the "Fubumio" same-day projection announced at the March EXPO venue, "Okakoro" figures were also announced. Did you see them?
また昨日から新作フィギュアは付属エコから受注は開始ということで、皆さん予約したかー！
Also, starting yesterday, orders for the new figures have begun from the included eco... Everyone, have you pre-ordered?!
え、めっちゃ可愛かった？めっちゃ可愛かった。
Huh, weren't they super cute? They were super duper cute.
イベントの開催を記念しまして、8月7日までにここスタジオを予約してくれた方には特典のステッカーをプレゼントだそうです！欲しい、欲しい！
To commemorate the event, those who pre-ordered Coco Studio by August 7th will receive a special sticker present! I want it, I want it!
そしてね、あの「おかころ」出たんですけども「フブミオ」が終わっちゃった、と思ってたんですが、なんと期間限定で「フブミオ」の追加予約も開始してます！
And also, we released "Okakoro", but while you might have thought "Fubumio" is over, amazingly, additional reservations for "Fubumio" have also started for a limited time!
最強、最高！お願いします！ぜひともゲーマーズ4人揃えれる方は揃えてみろ！
Strongest, best! Please! Everyone who can gather all four Gamers, try gathering them!
そして最後にカンダフル様による共催企業グッズ「超々超々ポップコーン」「超々超々グリルチキン」です！
And lastly, co-sponsored corporate goods by Kandaful: "Super Super Super Super Popcorn" and "Super Super Super Super Grilled Chicken"!
今回のイベントのビジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことで、ポップコーンは税込み1000円、缶詰めは税込み1500円で販売です！
Featuring visuals from this event splashed all over the design, popcorn is sold for 1,000 yen tax included, and canned goods for 1,500 yen tax included!
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、缶詰めはグリルチキンになってます！イエーイイエーイ！
The popcorn is salted caramel flavor, and the canned goods are grilled chicken! Yay yay!
なんとサイバーグッズストアではこちらのポップコーンと缶詰めが完売になってしまった！えーー！
Amazingly, at the Cyber Goods Store, this popcorn and canned goods have already sold out! Eeeeeh?!
なんと本日22時から追加販売が決定しました！
Amazingly, additional sales have been decided starting at 22:00 today!
こちらのグッズは他のグッズと異なり、受注販売ではなく数量限定商品のためご注意ください！
Please note that unlike other goods, these are in limited quantities rather than made-to-order!
サイバーグッズストアのほかにカンダフル公式通販サイトでも販売してますので皆さんチェックをお願いします！
They are also sold on Kandaful's official online store besides Cyber Goods Store, so please check it out!
集合アクリルパネルも含めてですね、文字語ですが購入できないグッズなので皆さんぜひ確認してください！
Including the group acrylic panel, these are goods you can't buy later on, so please make sure to check them out!
またでしょ、おい出せゲマズレスターにほら。パパッとパパッと！
Also, come on, hurry and show them, Gamers listeners! Quickly, quickly!
終点、終点。え、終わっちゃった？
Final stop, final stop. Huh, is it over?
え、また昨日続きまして、本日は韓国のライブビューイングも開催されてます！韓国の皆さん見てますか？
Also, following yesterday, today a live viewing in South Korea is also being held! Are you watching, everyone in Korea?
カウントダウン行くぞ！せーの、い、や、や、や！韓国のみんな！
Let's do a countdown! Ready, 1, 2, 3, 4! Everyone in Korea!
終わった後とか始まる前とかにやっぱ集合写真いっぱい撮ってくださってて、あの、ポーズも確認させていただきました！今日もよろしくお願いします！
They took lots of group photos after it ended and before it started, and we checked out their poses too! Thanks again today!
さあ、では早速ですね、最初に起こるゲームタイトル発表していきましょうかね！
Now then, let's quickly announce the first game title!
はい、いきますよ！
Alright, here we go!
せーの！こんにちわー！
Ready, set, hello!
ギャングビースト！
Gang Beasts!
はい、こちらはゼリーのようにふにゃふにゃなキャラクターたちが
Here, jello-like, floppy characters
危険なステージでドタバタ乱闘を繰り広げる、ちょっとおバカなマルチプレイヤーパーティゲームです！
fight in hazardous stages in this silly multiplayer party game!
今回は2対2のチーム戦と個人戦の2マッチで対決したいと思います！
This time, we'll compete in two matches: a 2-on-2 team battle and a solo battle!
いえーい！
Yay!
こちら勝利すると、頭の後ろにですね、星のバルーンがつきます。
If you win here, a star balloon will appear behind your head.
最終的にバルーンが一番多い人が勝利となります！
Whoever has the most balloons at the end wins!
ということで、早速やっていきますよー！
With that said, let's get right into it!
じゃ、最初のマッチは2対2のチーム戦ということで、
So, our first match is a 2-on-2 team battle,
チームはそうですね、先ほどあみだで決めました。
and the teams were decided earlier by amida.
フブオカチームとミオコロチーム。
Fubuoka team and Miokoro team.
おっ、はい、よろしくお願いします。
Oh, right! Let's do our best.
ふたりは仲良し万歳三唱です！
So, you two will do a banzai cheer for friendship!
ということでこちらでね、対決していきたいと思います！
With that, we'll have our battle here!
あれ、でもなんか、みなさんなんか、ないんですか？
Wait, do you guys not have anything?
え？何がですか？
Huh? What do you mean?
え、なんかこう掛け声とかチームメイトとか？
Like, a rally cry or team spirit?
ありますよ！
We do!
え、じゃあ教えてください。
Then please tell us.
まずは、お姉ちゃんの、可愛い……
First is, big sis's cute...
もっとのふぶちゃんです！
...even cuter Fubu-chan!
2人合わせて、ヤングコーンしまーす！
Together, we're 'Young Corn'!
えっ、あの、ずっといいですか？
Wait, is this really okay?
だめです。
No.
えっ、だめなのかな？
Really not?
なんか弱み握られてない？なんかちょっと握られてたかもしれない。
Aren't you being blackmailed? - Maybe I was a bit...
レトロな空気に流されている。あら、準備できてたからほら。
Swept away by the retro vibe. - We're ready, look!
後ろにコントローラーがある。おー、すいやんらしい。
There's a controller in the back. - So Suiyan-like.
自分のカラー取ってね、ちゃんとに！
Pick your own color properly!
はい、ということで、コントローラーでやっていきたいと思います！ではゲーム画面に切り替えてください！
Alright, let's play with controllers! Please switch to the game screen!
なんか両手上げてますけど（笑）
You guys are raising both hands (laughs)
これ誰が参加者か、みんな分かんないんじゃない？
Won't everyone be confused about who's who?
じゃ、担当者を紹介しよう！
Now let's introduce who's who!
まずですね、これ、青い来て、なんか白衣着てるのが
First off, the one wearing blue and a lab coat
どうやら白上さんだそうです。
seems to be Shirakami-san.
そしてそのお隣が、髪飾りの猫の被り物をかぶってるのが僕です！
And next to her, wearing the cat hair accessory, is me!
そしてえっと、なんか真っ赤っかな、えっと、なんか猫耳っぽいのがウチです。大神ミオです。
And, um, the super red one with cat ears is me, Oami Mio.
「ヤッホー！」みたいなやつがコーネ。「ヤッホー！」みたいなやつ。
The one saying 'Yahoo!' is Korone. The one saying 'Yahoo!'.
ということで、まずは赤と青に分かれましてチーム戦でございます。
So, split into Red and Blue for the team battle!
じゃあ、準備いいですか？おー！
Ready? - Oh!
はい、それでは、ギャングビースト1回戦です！スタート！
Alright, then! Gang Beasts Round 1! Start!
やるところね、頑張れ、頑張ろ、顔を見せてやろう。
Let's do our best and show them!
いけるのか？いけるよ。
Can we do it? - We can!
ファイト！おら！
Fight! Take this!
やばい！
Oh no!
おらおらおらおら！
Take that, take that!
やばい！落ちる！
Oh no, I'm falling!
やばい、やばい！
Help, help!
やめろ！
Stop it!
待って、これ何これ？
Wait, what is this?!
やめろ！やめろ！
Stop it! Stop!
やばい、やばい、やばい！
Ah, no, no, no!
離して、離して！
Let go, let go!
やばい、やばい、やばい！
Ahhh!
やばい、落ちる、落ちる！
I'm gonna fall!
助けて！どこ？
Help! Where are you?
手伝って！もう無理！
Help me! I can't do this!
何やってんのー！
What are you doing?!
もう死んじゃった！
I'm already dead!
やめて、やめて！
Stop it, stop!
レッドの勝利！
Red wins!
ということで、1回戦はレッドチームでした。
And so, Red team won the first round.
2戦先勝なので、あと2回勝ったチームが勝利ですからね。
It's first to 2 wins, so whichever team wins next takes the victory!
おー！やったー！
Yay!
あ！
Ah!
もう始まっちゃう！始まっちゃう！
It's starting! It's starting!
まるでプロレスだね、これ！
It's just like professional wrestling!
ほら、髪留めが
Hey, the hair clip—
髪留めが！
The hair clip!
ほら、つかんで！
Hey, grab on!
やれ！やれ！いけ！いけ！
Do it! Do it! Go! Go!
お兄ちゃん、いけ！いけ！
Go, big bro! Go!
お兄ちゃん、やれ！
Get 'em, big bro!
よし！やれ！やれ！
Alright! Get 'em!
いけ！
Go!
ブルーの勝利
Blue wins!
やばい！
Oh no!
赤の暴力！やばいよ、ねこたんね！
Red's brutality! That's bad, Neko-tan!
いった！木を頑張れ！木を頑張れ！
Ouch! Do your best, tree! Do your best, tree!
あそこに落ち込もうぜ！
Let's drop down over there!
やばい、危ない！これ！
Oh no, watch out!
中村、中邑！
Nakamura! Nakamura!
やばい！削り落とせ！
Crap! Knock 'em off!
やれ！やれ！落とせ！落とせ！
Do it! Knock 'em off!
いや、それ落ちるじゃん！
Hey, you're gonna fall!
落ちそうになった！
I almost fell!
ほら！ほら！いけ！
Hey! Go!
走れ！走れ！
Run! Run!
落ちる！落ちる！
They're falling!
あぶな！危ない！いけ！いけ！
Woah! Watch out! Go! Go!
逃げろ！逃げろ！なす今日もの！
Run! Run! Today's victim too!
揉み殻から逃げよう！
Let's get away from the chaff!
やばい！やばい！落とせ！
Crap! Knock 'em off!
お兄ちゃん！逃げろ！やばい！
Big bro! Run away! Oh no!
穴の横をよけろ！
Avoid the edge of the hole!
ほら！ほら！いけ！いけ！
Hey! Go! Go!
危ない！いけ！いけ！
Careful! Go! Go!
よし！落とせ！落とせ！
Alright! Knock 'em off!
早く！早く！
Hurry! Hurry!
最後の一匹！
The last one!
やばい！やばい！
Oh no! Oh no!
残り3秒！
3 seconds left!
落とせ！落とせ！
Knock 'em off!
よっしゃー！いけ！
All right! Go!
おかゆ！どうする？
Okayu! What should we do?
ころね、をやるしかねえ！
Korone, we have no choice but to do it!
やばい！やばい！ほら！ほら！
Oh no! Look! Look!
やれ！やれ！いけ！いけ！
Do it! Go! Go!
やれ！やれ！
Do it!
ブルーの勝利
Blue wins!
息ずれのミョウンダ
Myeon-da of breath trail
ということで、負けたの数舞は...
And so, the loser's score is...
え？負けた？負けたの数舞は？
Eh? Lost? The loser's score is?
地・地・地...（数が少ない！）じゃあ、二人合わせて？
Earth, earth, earth... (low count!) So, together?
4点？じゃあ、こっちは102こ...
4 points? Then, this side is 102...
ということで、今回はニャンコチームの...
And so, this time, the Nyanko team...
負けちゃったよ〜！
Lost~!
え、突然ですが、ここで...
Eh, out of nowhere, here is...
お知らせでございまーーす！
an announcement~!
無料配信をご覧の皆さまはここまでとなります。
This is where the free stream ends for everyone watching.
引き続きご覧になりたい方はABEMA PPVにてチケットのご購入をお願い致します！
If you wish to continue watching, please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
バイバーイ！痛いよね！
Bye-bye! It hurts, right?
この後個人戦が待ってますからね、バチバチにやっていきたいと思いますよ！
Individual matches await after this, so we're gonna go all out!
それでは、まったねー！
Well then, see you later!
FEBRUARY
Are you ready?
Coronation
Countdown
FEBRUARY
Cooking
Neo
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
Check the QR code for streaming details!
購入者特典 オリジナルボイスドラマと限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像がもらえる！
Bonus: Get an original voice drama and special message live image!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion has ended.
The full version is available on ABEMA PPV!